{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Outdoor \u0026 Landscape Lighting Installation Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39801/":{"taskOID":39801,"originalTaskOID":39801,"setID":324,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4017,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Lighting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the landscape lighting?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5539,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Security","answerDisplayText":"Security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent","answerDisplayText":"Accent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4478,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoor sculpture","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor sculpture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3599,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lighting pathway","answerDisplayText":"Lighting pathway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3596,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighting driveway","answerDisplayText":"Lighting driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2247,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entry lighting","answerDisplayText":"Entry lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4018,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Lighting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of landscape lighting is needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","answerDisplayText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":594,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent bullets (directionals)","answerDisplayText":"Accent bullets (directionals)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2066,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Down lighting (walls, tree, ceiling mount)","answerDisplayText":"Down lighting (walls, tree, ceiling mount)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1075,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bollard lights (garden lights)","answerDisplayText":"Bollard lights (garden lights)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6085,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Step or path lights (side lighting)","answerDisplayText":"Step or path lights (side lighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway markers","answerDisplayText":"Driveway markers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6589,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Underwater well lights","answerDisplayText":"Underwater well lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6628,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Uplighting","answerDisplayText":"Uplighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5696,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Silhouetting","answerDisplayText":"Silhouetting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11233,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7188,"questionDisplayText":"# of lights","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately how many landscaping lights do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11234,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11235,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11236,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-15","answerDisplayText":"6-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11233,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4017,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Lighting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the landscape lighting?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5539,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Security","answerDisplayText":"Security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent","answerDisplayText":"Accent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4478,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoor sculpture","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor sculpture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3599,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lighting pathway","answerDisplayText":"Lighting pathway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3596,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighting driveway","answerDisplayText":"Lighting driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2247,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entry lighting","answerDisplayText":"Entry lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5539,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Security","answerDisplayText":"Security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent","answerDisplayText":"Accent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4478,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoor sculpture","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor sculpture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3599,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lighting pathway","answerDisplayText":"Lighting pathway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3596,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighting driveway","answerDisplayText":"Lighting driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2247,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entry lighting","answerDisplayText":"Entry lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4018,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Lighting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of landscape lighting is needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","answerDisplayText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":594,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent bullets (directionals)","answerDisplayText":"Accent bullets (directionals)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2066,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Down lighting (walls, tree, ceiling mount)","answerDisplayText":"Down lighting (walls, tree, ceiling mount)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1075,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bollard lights (garden lights)","answerDisplayText":"Bollard lights (garden lights)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6085,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Step or path lights (side lighting)","answerDisplayText":"Step or path lights (side lighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway markers","answerDisplayText":"Driveway markers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6589,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Underwater well lights","answerDisplayText":"Underwater well lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6628,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Uplighting","answerDisplayText":"Uplighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5696,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Silhouetting","answerDisplayText":"Silhouetting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11233,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","answerDisplayText":"In-ground well lights (moonlighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":594,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Accent bullets (directionals)","answerDisplayText":"Accent bullets (directionals)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2066,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Down lighting (walls, tree, ceiling mount)","answerDisplayText":"Down lighting (walls, tree, ceiling mount)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1075,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bollard lights (garden lights)","answerDisplayText":"Bollard lights (garden lights)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6085,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Step or path lights (side lighting)","answerDisplayText":"Step or path lights (side lighting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Driveway markers","answerDisplayText":"Driveway markers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6589,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Underwater well lights","answerDisplayText":"Underwater well lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6628,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Uplighting","answerDisplayText":"Uplighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5696,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Silhouetting","answerDisplayText":"Silhouetting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11233,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7188,"questionDisplayText":"# of lights","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately how many landscaping lights do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11234,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11235,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11236,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-15","answerDisplayText":"6-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11233,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11234,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11235,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11236,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-15","answerDisplayText":"6-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11233,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/39801/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39801,"taskName":"Outdoor Lighting - Plan and Install","taskDescription":"Plan and Install Landscape Lighting","xmTaskDescriptor":"Outdoor \u0026 Landscape Lighting Installation Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":153,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Outdoor Lighting backyard landscape lamps","textMessagingName":"Inst Outdoor Light","rolloverLongDesc":"Specialists who have detailed knowledge of fixtures \u0026 wiring techniques. Know how to use exterior lighting to enhance safety, security \u0026 the beauty of a property.","rolloverShortDesc":"Exterior lighting for buildings \u0026 grounds.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Plan and Install Landscape Lighting.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Outdoor \u0026 Landscape Lighting Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Outdoor Lighting Companies","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Outdoor Lighting Plan \u0026 Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Outdoor Lighting - Plan and Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Outdoor Lighting Project","urlName":"Outdoor-Lighting-Plan-and-Install","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Outdoor Lighting Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Landscape Lighting Services","searchKeywords":"Outdoor,Lighting,backyard,landscape,lamps,yard,lawn","emcCategoryOid":-12046,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":324,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}